as glad as we are to see you you must
understand
we have to be careful relax girlfriend i
just drop by for some eminem and then
i'll be on my way
m and m my fave oh daddy please please
please can she stay
just stay out of trouble okay
Sonia the alarm went off at the house we
thought someone was breaking into the
factory
someone is I told you she'd be trouble
daddy
what is going on huh don't listen to her
honey
come on let's go
no daddy wait you knew didn't you
oh daddy how could you believe it or not
Mindy
i did it for you when you have children
of your own
maybe you'll understand I wanted to keep
you safe and happy
if I said no to Robotnik he'd take
everything away
and I couldn't let him do that to my
little girl
[Applause]
[Music]
believe me Mindy i'd love to knock that
pompous bullying blowfish rotund Nick on
his big round
butt oh daddy I don't need shopping and
facials and Manicures
no well I could cut back
i know I could definitely cut back
i want to be a freedom fighter like
Sonia I want to live life on the run
enemies around every corner
we sure do Sleet and Dingo are going to
come back Sonia manik and i'll get the
shipment ready for the furball twins
come on Mindy we haven't got much time
pack only the bare essentials
right you think my aerobicizer mini gym
will fit in our luggage oh
you think you'll look better in the
forest blue or red
[Music]
neither look good in Robotnik's dungeon
let's go
[Music]
Mindy leave them oh oh all right
no don't go I rolled out your carpet for
you
[Music]
run for it Mindy
yes to freedom
[Music]
hey what's going on
right we did it strike one for Mobius
good work yippee
[Music]
take a long look honey it may be the
last time you see it
it's hard to leave home hey
but you still get to hang with your dad
that's right
that's all that matters it sure is
home is where your family is